<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="title">
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 1</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 2</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 3</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 4</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 5</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 6</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 7</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 8</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 9</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 10</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 11</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 12</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 13</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 14</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 15</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 16</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 17</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 18</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 19</item>
        <item>หัวข้อที่ 20</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="detail">
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 1 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 2 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 3 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 4 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 5 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 6 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 7 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 8 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 9 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 10 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 11 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 12 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 13 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 14 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 15 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 16 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 17 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 18 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 19 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>
        <item>รายละเอียดที่ 20 It has roots in a piece of classical Latin literature from 45 BC, making it over 2000 years old.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>